{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0000", "question": "What is the host's name for Amazing One Bedroom Apartment in Prime Brooklyn in Bushwick?", "answer": "Alan"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0001", "question": "What is the host's name for Bright, Quiet Astoria 1 Bedroom near trains, MoMi in Astoria?", "answer": "Collin"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0002", "question": "What is the host's name for ★Designer 3BR Apt★ In Times Square in Hell's Kitchen?", "answer": "Vivian"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0003", "question": "What is the host's name for Spacious 3BR Apt - 12 Min to Manhattan in Long Island City?", "answer": "Timo"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0004", "question": "What is the host's name for Charming brownstone apartment in Columbia St?", "answer": "Chapman"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0005", "question": "What is the host's name for Large Room in Trendy Bushwick - 4 in Bushwick?", "answer": "Anthony"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0006", "question": "What is the host's name for Sanabria’s house in Bushwick?", "answer": "Edwin"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0007", "question": "What is the host's name for Luxury Wellness Space - Breathtaking NYC Views in Long Island City?", "answer": "Sara"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0008", "question": "What is the host's name for Brooklyn's heart, Ft Greene! in Fort Greene?", "answer": "Andrew"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0009", "question": "What is the host's name for 1 BEDROOM ASTORIA APARTMENT / 15 min to Manhattan in Astoria?", "answer": "Kijin"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0010", "question": "How many days are Cozy 2 bedroom 5min LGA/15min JFK  on main floor (id: 32113500) available during a year (365 days)?", "answer": "347"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0011", "question": "How many days are Cozy Brooklyn Room (id: 32595105) available during a year (365 days)?", "answer": "99"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0012", "question": "How many days are Private bathroom and bedroom for 1 -2 people (id: 14295197) available during a year (365 days)?", "answer": "0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0013", "question": "How many days are Cute Studio in Bushwick BK, NYC (id: 3286753) available during a year (365 days)?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0014", "question": "How many days are 20 mins to Times Square!  Vibrant NYC neighborhood (id: 52276316) available during a year (365 days)?", "answer": "107"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0015", "question": "How many days are Large BR in Spacious Artist Loft (id: 47523222) available during a year (365 days)?", "answer": "135"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0016", "question": "How many days are Brooklyn Garden Apartment (id: 15163413) available during a year (365 days)?", "answer": "51"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0017", "question": "How many days are MINIMALISTIC APARTMENT/DECK IN HISTORIC BROWNSTONE (id: 16455242) available during a year (365 days)?", "answer": "343"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0018", "question": "How many days are Location! Location! Location! ... in a cute studio (id: 42878931) available during a year (365 days)?", "answer": "0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0019", "question": "How many days are Elegant Large One Bed  / 1.5 Bathroom-  UWS (id: 48875805) available during a year (365 days)?", "answer": "325"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0020", "question": "What is the room type of Spacious Room in Great Neighborhood (id: 8266290) in Clinton Hill?", "answer": "Private room"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0021", "question": "What is the room type of Charming East Village Apartment (id: 1867895) in East Village?", "answer": "Entire home/apt"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0022", "question": "What is the room type of Cute, spacious room in Crown Heights (id: 13713073) in Crown Heights?", "answer": "Private room"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0023", "question": "What is the room type of Cozy Apartment - Try NYC Living! (id: 52815913) in Long Island City?", "answer": "Entire home/apt"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0024", "question": "What is the room type of MODERN APARTMENT MINUTES AWAY FROM MANHATTAN (id: 27014666) in Kingsbridge?", "answer": "Entire home/apt"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0025", "question": "What is the room type of Private room, modern apartment w/ PRIVATE ROOF! (id: 16693836) in Williamsburg?", "answer": "Private room"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0026", "question": "What is the room type of Room for rent - Right by Bedford ave L train (id: 28307600) in Williamsburg?", "answer": "Private room"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0027", "question": "What is the room type of Industrial Modernism Flex 2br Loft! (id: 2952060) in Greenpoint?", "answer": "Entire home/apt"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0028", "question": "What is the room type of GARDEN UTOPIA, UES; SUPERIOR LOCATION & AMENITIES (id: 18737898) in Upper East Side?", "answer": "Entire home/apt"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0029", "question": "What is the room type of Large private bedroom&bath 2 min. away from subway (id: 42892739) in Williamsburg?", "answer": "Private room"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0030", "question": "What is the price of Spacious 2 BR Bedford Stuyvesant Bklyn NY (id: 44668936) in Bedford-Stuyvesant?", "answer": "$479 "}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0031", "question": "What is the price of Centrally  Located Beautiful Escape (id: 42418313) in East Flatbush?", "answer": "$828 "}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0032", "question": "What is the price of Perfect 1 Bedroom in Manhattan,close to everything (id: 33393179) in Hell's Kitchen?", "answer": "$572 "}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0033", "question": "What is the price of 4Js Room4You (id: 54980377) in East Flatbush?", "answer": "$348 "}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0034", "question": "What is the price of Spacious 5 Bedroom Apt Williamsburg (id: 47825330) in Williamsburg?", "answer": "$87 "}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0035", "question": "What is the price of Tranquil Columbus Cir. 1BR, Doorman, River Views by Blueground (id: 22381421) in Upper West Side?", "answer": "$1,146 "}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0036", "question": "What is the price of Your Quiet Refuge in the Heart of Manhattan (id: 45850305) in Civic Center?", "answer": "$1,150 "}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0037", "question": "What is the price of Beautiful, spacious 2 bed, Crown Heights apartment (id: 54098906) in Brownsville?", "answer": "$629 "}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0038", "question": "What is the price of Brooklyn oasis with breathtaking skyline view! (id: 40452125) in Bedford-Stuyvesant?", "answer": "$799 "}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0039", "question": "What is the price of Sun drenched loft like space with private yard (id: 18732928) in Williamsburg?", "answer": "$632 "}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0040", "question": "What is the minimum number of nights of Entire APT in Center of Park Slope Brooklyn (id: 11466316) in South Slope?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0041", "question": "What is the minimum number of nights of #Awesome 2 BR Flat Times Square! (id: 18268996) in Hell's Kitchen?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0042", "question": "What is the minimum number of nights of Beautiful douplex with garden in crown heights!! (id: 45622205) in Crown Heights?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0043", "question": "What is the minimum number of nights of TRUE2BR-PRIME MIDTOWN EAST~53rd&3rd (id: 7404150) in Midtown?", "answer": "30"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0044", "question": "What is the minimum number of nights of Luxurious Manhattan 1 Bedroom (id: 13026564) in Hell's Kitchen?", "answer": "30"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0045", "question": "What is the minimum number of nights of Charming Boutique Hotel in Chelsea New York (id: 30363813) in Chelsea?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0046", "question": "What is the minimum number of nights of Cozy, Quiet Apt near Times Square and Penn Station (id: 24179158) in Hell's Kitchen?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0047", "question": "What is the minimum number of nights of Vanderbilt  · Quaint Art-Filled Brooklyn Apartment (id: 46606956) in Clinton Hill?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0048", "question": "What is the minimum number of nights of 1br Apartment EastVillage,Manhattan (id: 10875908) in East Village?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0049", "question": "What is the minimum number of nights of Bushwick Duplex 3 min walk to subway (id: 19458650) in Bushwick?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0050", "question": "When was of Large Room in Queens (id: 44353020) in Rego Park constructed?", "answer": "2003"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0051", "question": "When was of Bright Apartment in Clinton Hill (id: 9290254) in Clinton Hill constructed?", "answer": "2012"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0052", "question": "When was of Huge Brownstone,Private Garden- Pet chicks & eggs. (id: 50048890) in Bedford-Stuyvesant constructed?", "answer": "2010"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0053", "question": "When was of The Orchid (id: 37122308) in Flatbush constructed?", "answer": "2013"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0054", "question": "When was of Stunning arty 3200sf 3FLR+3BR townhome w/terrace (id: 1228884) in Park Slope constructed?", "answer": "2016"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0055", "question": "When was of Bright 2-bedroom in Brooklyn (id: 22728818) in Bedford-Stuyvesant constructed?", "answer": "2022"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0056", "question": "When was of Charming and Convinient, LOCATION LOCATION! (id: 39064747) in Harlem constructed?", "answer": "2021"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0057", "question": "When was of Charming Carnegie Hill Bedroom (id: 20204255) in East Harlem constructed?", "answer": "2013"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0058", "question": "When was of Beautiful 1 bedroom apartment in Greenpoint, BK (id: 46392112) in Greenpoint constructed?", "answer": "2011"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0059", "question": "When was of big cozy room in Bed-Stuy with separate entrance (id: 50473056) in Bedford-Stuyvesant constructed?", "answer": "2009"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0060", "question": "How many reviews does Modern Manhattan Living Suite 2A (id: 3654033) in Harlem have?", "answer": "36"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0061", "question": "How many reviews does Private Room in WILLIAMSBURG (id: 3211088) in Williamsburg have?", "answer": "38"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0062", "question": "How many reviews does MASSIVE 8BR/8BTH Brooklyn Townhouse w/ Backyard (id: 30796264) in Bushwick have?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0063", "question": "How many reviews does A+ Location City Studio (Queen Bed & Futon) (id: 31064682) in Midtown have?", "answer": "36"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0064", "question": "How many reviews does Apartment with backyard in East Williamsburg (id: 43488118) in Williamsburg have?", "answer": "91"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0065", "question": "How many reviews does PRIVATE BIG ROOM w. Queen Bed, and quiet roommates (id: 42031151) in Melrose have?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0066", "question": "How many reviews does 1BR Loft: Cleaning CDC guidelines implemented (id: 36070177) in Greenpoint have?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0067", "question": "How many reviews does Cute & Cozy Studio in the heart of East Village (id: 23347946) in East Village have?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0068", "question": "How many reviews does Cozy Brownstone Apartment Near City (id: 56740557) in Bedford-Stuyvesant have?", "answer": "147"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0069", "question": "How many reviews does ✨Bright, spacious apartment in the West Village❤️ (id: 12394733) in West Village have?", "answer": "86"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0070", "question": "What is the last review date of Hudson Yards 1 Bedroom (LGBT friendly) (id: 27031235) in Hell's Kitchen?", "answer": NaN}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0071", "question": "What is the last review date of Large 1 bdrm with Modern finishes - Pelham Gardens (id: 17531123) in Pelham Gardens?", "answer": "7/4/2019"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0072", "question": "What is the last review date of LUXURY MURRAY HILL EAST 34TH~1BR (id: 15549470) in Murray Hill?", "answer": "6/23/2019"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0073", "question": "What is the last review date of Modern 2BR Apartment in Heart of East Village (id: 4618349) in East Village?", "answer": "1/1/2017"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0074", "question": "What is the last review date of Brand New Cozy Apt Upper West Manhattan (id: 20436773) in Upper West Side?", "answer": "6/24/2019"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0075", "question": "What is the last review date of Bright, Clean + Beautiful West Village 1 Bedroom (id: 15396483) in West Village?", "answer": "3/11/2019"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0076", "question": "What is the last review date of Clean, Safe, Convenient, Comfy (id: 3494971) in Harlem?", "answer": "9/29/2016"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0077", "question": "What is the last review date of One bedroom available in Astoria (id: 6316671) in Long Island City?", "answer": NaN}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0078", "question": "What is the last review date of Home For Medical Professionals - \"Laudanum\" (id: 29397288) in Bushwick?", "answer": "2/26/2022"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0079", "question": "What is the last review date of PRIVATE GARDEN APARTMENT IN HISTORIC BROWNSTONE (id: 37738123) in Bedford-Stuyvesant?", "answer": "11/7/2020"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0080", "question": "What is the review rate number of Cozy Manhattan view one bedroom . (id: 36526377) in Tompkinsville?", "answer": "4.0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0081", "question": "What is the review rate number of 138 Bowery-Bright Studio (id: 34458013) in Chinatown?", "answer": "3.0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0082", "question": "What is the review rate number of CENTRAL GORGEOUS STUDIO - HUGE PRIVATE TERRACE (id: 43367164) in East Village?", "answer": "2.0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0083", "question": "What is the review rate number of Trendy Chelsea 1BR w/ Balcony, Gym + Doorman by Blueground (id: 22336685) in Chelsea?", "answer": "2.0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0084", "question": "What is the review rate number of Beautiful, New, 1 BR, Heart of Williamsburg! (id: 10019843) in Williamsburg?", "answer": "4.0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0085", "question": "What is the review rate number of 2 Bedroom the NYs Most Poppin Neighborhood (id: 25770886) in Lower East Side?", "answer": "2.0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0086", "question": "What is the review rate number of Room in cool Bushwick loft! (id: 2130237) in Bedford-Stuyvesant?", "answer": "1.0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0087", "question": "What is the review rate number of Amazing View from Contemporary Loft (id: 39977147) in Midtown?", "answer": "3.0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0088", "question": "What is the review rate number of Charming Apartment in Brooklyn (id: 43284872) in Bedford-Stuyvesant?", "answer": "3.0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0089", "question": "What is the review rate number of Big Room in a Downtown Loft Apartment (id: 37089723) in Financial District?", "answer": "2.0"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0090", "question": "What is the average number of reviews per month of Hotel Room King Bed TSQ (id: 37421103) in Midtown?", "answer": "0.08"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0091", "question": "What is the average number of reviews per month of Big, Bright, Beautiful Room (id: 8857251) in Crown Heights?", "answer": "0.07"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0092", "question": "What is the average number of reviews per month of Charming 2brs w/ private garden in Carroll Gardens (id: 13763884) in Gowanus?", "answer": "0.19"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0093", "question": "What is the average number of reviews per month of Cozy home (id: 53206389) in Midwood?", "answer": "1.88"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0094", "question": "What is the average number of reviews per month of Steps from the Sand Studio (id: 28516922) in Belle Harbor?", "answer": "2.25"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0095", "question": "What is the average number of reviews per month of 1 Bedroom w/ common space in 4br Loft in Bushwick (id: 56440658) in Bedford-Stuyvesant?", "answer": "nan"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0096", "question": "What is the average number of reviews per month of Modern Private Bedroom-15min from the Manhattan! (id: 45618339) in Astoria?", "answer": "nan"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0097", "question": "What is the average number of reviews per month of Brooklyn's finest by Prospect Park (id: 40505698) in Prospect-Lefferts Gardens?", "answer": "1.37"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0098", "question": "What is the average number of reviews per month of One bedroom apartment in Brooklyn, NY (id: 22332819) in Park Slope?", "answer": "0.81"}
{"qid": "easy-airbnb-0099", "question": "What is the average number of reviews per month of Relax comfortably 1BR w/AC in the Heart of Queens1 (id: 27199687) in East Elmhurst?", "answer": "8.0"}
